Guide to the Lillian D. Wald Papers
Rare Book and Manuscript Library Columbia University Libraries
- Series III: General Subjects
  - Welfare Council. correspondence: 1931-1932 (Box 33, Folder 11.7)
  - Welfare Council. minutes: 1925 (Box 34, Folder 1.1)
  - Welfare Council. minutes: 1926-1928 (Box 34, Folder 1.2)
  - Welfare Council. minutes: 1929 (Box 34, Folder 1.3)
  - Welfare Council. minutes: 1930 (Box 34, Folder 1.4)
  - Welfare Council. minutes: 1931 (Box 34, Folder 1.5)
  - Welfare Council. minutes: 1932 (Box 34, Folder 1.6)
    On Reel 36 of the Wald Microfilm
  - Welfare Council, printed materials (Box 34, Folder 1.7)
  - Welfare Council, reports: n.d. (Box 34, Folder 1.8)
  - Welfare Council. reports: 1924 (Box 34, Folder 1.9)
  - Welfare Council. reports: 1927-1928 (Box 34, Folder 1.10)
  - Welfare Council. reports: 1929 (Box 34, Folder 1.11)
  - Welfare Council; reports: 1930 (Box 34, Folder 1.12)
  - Welfare Council, reports: 1931 (Box 34, Folder 1.13)
  - Welfare Council, reports: 1932 (Box 35, Folder 1.1)
    On Reel 37 of the Wald Microfilm
  - Welfare Council, reports: 1933 (Box 35, Folder 1.2)
  - Welfare Council, Emergency Unit Training School: correspondence (Box 35, Folder 1.3)
  - Welfare Council. Emergency Unit Training School: reports. etc. (Box 35, Folder 1.4)
  - Williams College, Institute of Politics (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - Women's Democratic Union, Inc. (Box 35, Folder 3)
  - Women's International League for Peace and Freedom, International: 1918-1922 (Box 35, Folder 4.1)
  - Women's International League for Peace and Freedom, International: 1927-1929 (Box 35, Folder 4.2)
  - Women's International League for Peace and Freedom International: 1930 (Box 35, Folder 4.3)
  - Women's International League for Peace and Freedom, International: 1931 (Box 35, Folder 4.4)
  - Women's International League for Peace and Freedom, International: 1932-1933 (Box 35, Folder 4.5)
  - Women's International League for Peace and Freedom, Massachusetts Branch (Box 35, Folder 4.6)
    On Reel 38 of the Wald Microfilm
  - Women's International League for Peace and Freedom; memoranda.. etc. (Box 35, Folder 4.7)
  - Women's International League for Peace and Freedom. National (Box 36, Folder 1.1)
  - Women's International League for Peace and Freedom. New York City (Box 36, Folder 1.2)
  - Women's International League for Peace and Freedom. New York State (Box 36, Folder 1.3)
  - Women's International League for Peace and Freedom. clippings (Box 36, Folder 1.4)
  - Women's International League for Peace and Freedom; pamphlets, etc. (Box 36, Folder 1.5)
  - The World Tomorrow (Box 36, Folder 2)
  - Working Girls' Vacation Society (Box 36, Folder 3)
  - World War I. correspondence (Box 36, Folder 4.1)
  - World War I. printed material (Box 36, Folder 4.2)
    On Reel 39 of the Wald Microfilm
  - World War I. American Chocolate Fund (Box 36, Folder 4.3)
  - World War I. American Legal Defense League (Box 36, Folder 4.4)
  - World War I, Council of Organizations (Box 36, Folder 4.5)
  - World War I, Council on National Defense: correspondence, 1917 (Box 36, Folder 4.6)
  - World War I. Council on National Defense: correspondence. 1918-1921 (Box 36, Folder 4.7)
  - World War I, Council on National Defense: memos, reports, etc. (Box 36, Folder 4.8)
  - World War I. Council on National Defense: printed materials (Box 37, Folder 1.1)
  - World War I. Council on National Defense: Committee on Nursing (Box 37, Folder 1.2)
  - World War I. Council on National Defense: General Medical Board (Box 37, Folder 1.3)
  - World War I. Council on National Defense: Mayor's Committee (Box 37, Folder 1.4)
    On Reel 40 of the Wald Microfilm
  - World War I, Council on National Defense: Military Census (Box 37, Folder 1.5)
  - World War I. Dutch mediation (Box 37, Folder 1.6)
  - World War I. food shortage: correspondence (Box 37, Folder 1.7)
  - World War I, food shortage: reports, pamphlets, etc. (Box 37, Folder 1.8)
  - World War I, fuel shortage (Box 37, Folder 1.9)
  - World War I, Henry Street Settlement activities (Box 37, Folder 1.10)
  - World War I, Henry Street Settlement staff overseas: miscellaneous (Box 37, Folder 1.11)
  - World War I. Henry Street Settlement staff overseas: Tredale (Box 37, Folder 1.12)
  - World War I, Henry Street Settlement staff overseas: Whedon (Box 37, Folder 1.13)
  - World War I, reconstruction: correspondence (Box 38, Folder 1.1)
    On Reel 41 of the Wald Microfilm
  - World War I, reconstruction: printed materials (Box 38, Folder 1.2)
  - World War I, reconstruction: National Industrial Conference 1919. 1 (Box 38, Folder 1.3)
  - World War I, reconstruction: National Industrial Conference 1919 2 (Box 38, Folder 1.4)
  - World War I, reconstruction: National Industrial Conference 1919 3 (Box 38, Folder 1.5)
  - World War I, War Department (Box 38, Folder 1.6)
  - Y (miscellaneous) (Box 38, Folder 2)
    On Reel 42 of the Wald Microfilm
  - Yale Placement Bureau (Box 38, Folder 3)
  - Y.M.C.A. (Box 38, Folder 4)
  - Y.W.C.A. (Box 38, Folder 5)
- Series IV: Children
  - General correspondence (Box 39, Folder 1.1)
  - General printed material (Box 39, Folder 1.2)
  - Babies' Welfare Federation (Box 39, Folder 3)
  - Boy Scouts (Box 39, Folder 4)
  - Boys' Club Federation, 1926-1928 (Box 39, Folder 4.1)
  - Boys' Club Federation, 1929 (Box 39, Folder 4.2)
  - Boys' Club Federation, 1930 (Box 39, Folder 4.3)
  - Boys' Club Federation, 1931 (Box 39, Folder 4.4)
  - Boys' Club Federation. 1932 (Box 39, Folder 4.5)
  - Child Study Association (Box 39, Folder 5)
  - Child Welfare Committee of America (Box 39, Folder 6)
    On Reel 43 of the Wald Microfilm
  - "Children" (magazine) (Box 39, Folder 7)
  - Children's Aid Society (Box 39, Folder 8)
  - Children's Courts (Box 39, Folder 9)
  - Children's Welfare Federation, 1924-1925 (Box 39, Folder 10.1)
  - Children's Welfare Federation. 1926-1928 (Box 39, Folder 10.2)
  - Children's Welfare Federation, 1929-1932 (Box 39, Folder 10.3)
  - Children's Year. 1918-1919 correspondence (Box 39, Folder 11.1)
  - Children's Year. 1918-1919 memoranda (Box 39, Folder 11.2)
  - Children's Year, 1918-1919 printed materials (Box 39, Folder 11.3)
  - Committee for Federal Relief for Children (Box 39, Folder 12)
  - Committee to "Save the Children's Lives" (Box 39, Folder 13)
  - Community Youth of New York (Box 39, Folder 14)
  - George Junior Republic (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - Girl Scouts (Box 40, Folder 2)
  - Heckscher Foundation for Children (Box 40, Folder 3)
  - Henry Street Settlement, Baby Show, 1925 (Box 40, Folder 4)
  - Kips Bay Boys' Club (Box 40, Folder 5)
  - Milk and Child Health Campaign (Box 40, Folder 6)
  - Milk for Children of America (Box 40, Folder 7)
  - National Child Labor Committee, 1904-1913 (Box 40, Folder 8.1)
  - National Child Labor Committee, 1914-1915 (Box 40, Folder 8.2)
  - National Child Labor Committee, 1916 (Box 40, Folder 8.3)
  - National Child Labor Committee, 1917 (Box 40, Folder 8.4)
  - National Child Labor Committee" 1918 (Box 40, Folder 8.5)
  - National Child Labor Committee, 1919-1921 (Box 40, Folder 8.6)
  - National Child Labor Committee, 1922-1923 (Box 40, Folder 8.7)
  - National Child Labor Committee, 1924 (Box 40, Folder 8.8)
    On Reel 44 of the Wald Microfilm
  - National Child Labor Committee, 1925 (Box 40, Folder 8.9)
  - National Child Labor Committee. 1926 (Box 40, Folder 8.10)
  - National Child Labor Committee. 1927 (Box 40, Folder 8.11)
  - National Child Labor Committee. 1928 (Box 40, Folder 8.12)
  - National Child Labor Committee, 1929 (Box 40, Folder 8.13)
  - National Child Labor Committee. 1930 and undated (Box 40, Folder 8.14)
  - National Child Labor Committee. newsboys (Box 40, Folder 9)
  - National Child Welfare Association (Box 40, Folder 10)
  - National Child Welfare Exhibit (Box 40, Folder 11)
  - New York Child Labor Committee, 1903-1908 (Box 41, Folder 1.1)
  - New York Child Labor Committee, 1909 (Box 41, Folder 1.2)
  - New York Child Labor Committee, 1911 (Box 41, Folder 1.3)
  - New York Child Labor Committee, 1912-1915 (Box 41, Folder 1.4)
  - New York Child Labor Committee, 1916-1917 (Box 41, Folder 1.5)
  - New York Child Labor Committee. 19J8-19J9 (Box 41, Folder 1.6)
  - New York Child Labor Committee, 1920-1925 (Box 41, Folder 1.7)
    On Reel 45 of the Wald Microfilm
  - New York Child Labor Committee, 1926 (Box 41, Folder 1.8)
  - New York Child Labor Committee, 1927 (Box 41, Folder 1.9)
  - New York Child Labor Committee, 1928 (Box 41, Folder 1.10)
  - New York Child Labor Committee, 1929 (Box 41, Folder 1.11)
  - New York Child Labor Committee, 1930 (Box 41, Folder 1.12)
  - New York Child Labor Committee, scholarships (Box 41, Folder 2)
  - New York Society for the Prevention of Cruelty to Children (Box 41, Folder 3)
  - Nursery schools (Box 41, Folder 4)
  - Pan-American Child Welfare Work. 1930-1931 (Box 41, Folder 5)
  - Pioneer Youth of America (Box 41, Folder 6)
  - United Parents Association (Box 41, Folder 7)
  - U.S. Department of Labor, Children's Bureau (Box 41, Folder 8)
  - White House Conference. 1931 1 (Box 41, Folder 9.1)
  - White House Conference, 1931 2 (Box 41, Folder 9.2)
  - White House Conference, 1933 (Box 41, Folder 10)
- Series V: Henry Street Settlement
  - Alumni Association, Theodore Siegel (Box 42, Folder 1)
    On Reel 46 of the Wald Microfilm
  - Athletics (Box 42, Folder 2)
  - Board of Delegates (Box 42, Folder 3)
  - Board of Directors; meetings, etc. (Box 42, Folder 4.1)
  - Board of Directors, miscellaneous correspondence (Box 42, Folder 4.2)
  - Board of Directors, John G. Agar (Box 42, Folder 4.3)
  - Board of Directors, George Alger (Box 42, Folder 4.4)
  - Board of Directors, Leo Arnstein (Box 42, Folder 4.5)
  - Board of Directors, Sylvan Bier (Box 42, Folder 4.6)
  - Board of Directors, Charles C. Burlingham (Box 42, Folder 4.7)
  - Board of Directors, Paul D. Cravath (Box 42, Folder 4.8)
  - Board of Directors, William Darrach (Box 42, Folder 4.9)
  - Board of Directors, L. E. Holt (Box 42, Folder 4.10)
  - Board of Directors, Nathalie Laimbeer (Box 42, Folder 4.11)
  - Board of Directors, Herbert H. Lehman. (Box 42, Folder 4.12)
  - Board of Directors, James H. Perkins (Box 42, Folder 4.13)
  - Board of Directors, Hyman Schroeder (Box 42, Folder 4.14)
  - Board of Directors, Arthur Stewart (Box 42, Folder 4.15)
  - Board of Directors, Felix Warburg (Box 42, Folder 4.16)
  - Boys Work Committee (Box 42, Folder 5)
    On Reel 47 of the Wald Microfilm
  - By-laws (Box 42, Folder 6)
  - Cabaret-dance, 1930 (Box 42, Folder 7)
  - Cases, A (Box 42, Folder 8.1)
  - Cases, B (Box 42, Folder 8.2)
  - Cases, Dora Bloom (Box 42, Folder 8.3)
  - Cases, Bromberg (Box 42, Folder 8.4)
  - Cases, C (Box 43, Folder 1.1)
  - Cases, D (Box 43, Folder 1.2)
  - Cases, E (Box 43, Folder 1.3)
  - Cases, F (Box 43, Folder 1.4)
  - Cases, A. Fario (Box 43, Folder 1.5)
  - Cases, G (Box 43, Folder 1.6)
  - Cases, Elizabeth Gannon (Box 43, Folder 1.7)
    On Reel 48 of the Wald Microfilm
  - Cases, Rose Graetz (Box 43, Folder 1.8)
  - Cases, H (Box 43, Folder 1.9)
  - Cases, Charles Haag (Box 43, Folder 1.10)
  - Cases, Sophia Hermalin (Box 43, Folder 1.11)
  - Cases, I (Box 43, Folder 1.12)
  - Cases, J (Box 43, Folder 1.13)
  - Cases, K (Box 43, Folder 1.14)
  - Cases, L (Box 43, Folder 1.15)
  - Cases, M (Box 43, Folder 1.16)
  - Cases, Stanley Millstein (Box 43, Folder 1.17)
  - Cases, Anna Molander (Box 43, Folder 1.18)
  - Cases, David Morgenstern (Box 43, Folder 1.19)
  - Cases, N (Box 43, Folder 1.20)
  - Cases, O (Box 43, Folder 1.21)
  - Cases, P (Box 44, Folder 1.1)
    On Reel 49 of the Wald Microfilm
  - Cases, Alice Cuttins Phelps (Box 44, Folder 1.2)
  - Cases, Q (Box 44, Folder 1.3)
  - Cues, R (Box 44, Folder 1.4)
  - Cases, S (Box 44, Folder 1.5)
  - Cases, Morris Salem (Box 44, Folder 1.6)
  - Cases, Sidney Scopp (Box 44, Folder 1.7)
  - Cases, Elizabeth Schatz (Box 44, Folder 1.8)
  - Cases, Jacob Shufro (Box 44, Folder 1.9)
  - Cases. Ruth Siegel (Box 44, Folder 1.10)
  - Cases, T (Box 44, Folder 1.11)
  - Cases, Taeler (Box 44, Folder 1.12)
  - Cases, U (Box 44, Folder 1.13)
  - Cases, V (Box 44, Folder 1.14)
  - Cases, W (Box 44, Folder 1.15)
    On Reel 50 of the Wald Microfilm
  - Cases, Y-Z (Box 44, Folder 1.16)
  - Centers, general correspondence (Box 44, Folder 2.1)
  - Centers; general lists, memos. etc. (Box 44, Folder 2.2)
  - Centers. Bronx centers (Box 44, Folder 2.3)
  - Centers. East Harlem: correspondence (Box 44, Folder 2.4)
  - Centers. East Harlem: reports. etc. (Box 44, Folder 2.5)
  - Centers, Fordham (Box 45, Folder 1.1)
  - Centers, Gouverneur St. (Box 45, Folder 1.2)
  - Centers. Hamilton House: 1918 (Box 45, Folder 1.3)
  - Centers. Hamilton House: 1919 (Box 45, Folder 1.4)
  - Centers. Hamilton House: 1920 (Box 45, Folder 1.5)
  - Centers. Hamilton House: 1921 (Box 45, Folder 1.6)
  - Centers, Hamilton House: 1922 (Box 45, Folder 1.7)
  - Centers, Hamilton House: 1923-1924 (Box 45, Folder 1.8)
  - Centers. Hamilton House: 1925 (Box 45, Folder 1.9)
    On Reel 51 of the Wald Microfilm
  - Centers, Hamilton House: 1926 (Box 45, Folder 1.10)
  - Centers, Hamilton House: 1927 (Box 45, Folder 1.11)
  - Centers, Hamilton House: 1928-1929 (Box 45, Folder 1.12)
  - Centers, Hamilton House: 1930 (Box 45, Folder 1.13)
  - Centers, Hamilton House: 1931-1932 (Box 45, Folder 1.14)
  - Centers. information (Box 45, Folder 1.15)
  - Centers. interhouse correspondence (Box 45, Folder 1.16)
  - Centers Lincoln House: Birdye Haynes Memorial Scholarship (Box 45, Folder 1.17)
  - Centers. Lincoln House: general correspondence (Box 45, Folder 1.18)
  - Centers. Lincoln House: directors’ correspondence (Box 45, Folder 1.19)
  - Centers. Lincoln House: directors’ meetings (Box 45, Folder 1.20)
    On Reel 52 of the Wald Microfilm
  - Centers. Lincoln House: farm gardens (Box 46, Folder 1.1)
  - Centers. Lincoln House: Kindergarten Association (Box 46, Folder 1.2)
  - Centers. Lincoln House: music classes (Box 46, Folder 1.3)
  - Centers. Lincoln House: printed material (Box 46, Folder 1.4)
  - Centers. Lincoln House: reports (Box 46, Folder 1.5)
  - Centers, Lincoln House: staff correspondence (Box 46, Folder 1.6)
  - Centers, Lincoln House: staff lists (Box 46, Folder 1.7)
  - Centers. Lincoln House: Westchester Association (Box 46, Folder 1.8)
  - Centers. Maternity Center (Box 46, Folder 1.9)
    On Reel 53 of the Wald Microfilm
  - Centers. Morningside (Box 46, Folder 1.10)
  - Centers. Melrose Center (Box 46, Folder 1.11)
  - Centers. Morris Avenue (Box 46, Folder 1.12)
  - Centers. 99 Park Avenue: 1927 (Box 46, Folder 1.13)
  - Centers. 99 Park Avenue: 1928 (Box 46, Folder 1.14)
  - Centers 99 Park Avenue: 1929 (Box 46, Folder 1.15)
  - Centers, 99 Park Avenue: 1930 (Box 46, Folder 1.16)
  - Centers. 99 Park Avenue: 1931-1933 (Box 46, Folder 1.17)
  - Centers. 79th Street Branch, 1906-1913 and n.d. (Box 47, Folder 1.1)
  - Centers, 79th Street Branch, 1914-1916 (Box 47, Folder 1.2)
  - Centers, 79th Street Branch, 1917 (Box 47, Folder 1.3)
  - Centers, 79th Street Branch, 1918 (Box 47, Folder 1.4)
  - Centers. 79th Street Branch, 1919 (Box 47, Folder 1.5)
  - Centers, 79th Street Branch, 1920-1921 (Box 47, Folder 1.6)
  - Centers, 79th Street Branch, 1922-1924 (Box 47, Folder 1.7)
    On Reel 54 of the Wald Microfilm
  - Centers, 79th Street Branch, 1925 (Box 47, Folder 1.8)
  - Centers, 79th Street Branch, 1926 (Box 47, Folder 1.9)
  - Centers. 79th Street Branch, 1927. correspondence (Box 47, Folder 1.10)
  - Centers. 79th Street Branch, 1927. minutes (Box 47, Folder 1.11)
  - Centers. 79th Street Branch, 1927. statistical study (Box 47, Folder 1.12)
  - Centers, 79th Street Branch, 1928 (Box 47, Folder 1.13)
  - Centers, 79th Street Branch, 1929-1930 (Box 47, Folder 1.14)
  - Centers, 79th Street Branch, 1931-1932 (Box 47, Folder 1.15)
  - Centers. Spuyten Duyvil (Box 47, Folder 1.16)
  - Centers. Staten Island: correspondence (Box 47, Folder 1.17)
  - Centers. Staten Island: reports (Box 47, Folder 1.18)
  - Centers. Stuyvesant (Box 47, Folder 1.19)
  - Centers. Tremont (Box 47, Folder 1.20)
  - Centers. Villa Avenue (Box 47, Folder 1.21)
  - Christmas parties (Box 47, Folder 2)
  - Clubs. n.d. (Box 48, Folder 1.1)
    On Reel 55 of the Wald Microfilm
  - Clubs, 1900-1909 (Box 48, Folder 1.2)
  - Clubs, 1910-1913 (Box 48, Folder 1.3)
  - Clubs, 1914-1916 (Box 48, Folder 1.4)
  - Clubs, 1917-1923 (Box 48, Folder 1.5)
  - Clubs, 1924-1928 (Box 48, Folder 1.6)
  - Clubs, 1929 (Box 48, Folder 1.7)
  - Clubs, 1930-1931 (Box 48, Folder 1.8)
  - Clubs, 1932-1933 (Box 48, Folder 1.9)
  - Clubs, American Hero Club (Box 48, Folder 1.10)
  - Clubs, Bluebird Club (Box 48, Folder 1.11)
  - Clubs. Constitutions (Box 48, Folder 1.12)
  - Clubs, Governing Board (Box 48, Folder 1.13)
  - Clubs, Leader Training Course (Box 48, Folder 1.14)
  - Clubs, Mens' C1ub (Box 48, Folder 1.15)
    On Reel 56 of the Wald Microfilm
  - Clubs, Mothers' Club (Box 48, Folder 1.16)
  - Conference, November 1932 (Box 48, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, A (Box 49, Folder 1.1)
  - Correspondence, B (Box 49, Folder 1.2)
  - Correspondence, C (Box 49, Folder 1.3)
    On Reel 57 of the Wald Microfilm
  - Correspondence, D (Box 49, Folder 1.4)
  - Correspondence, E (Box 49, Folder 1.5)
  - Correspondence, F (Box 49, Folder 1.6)
  - Correspondence, G (Box 49, Folder 1.7)
  - Correspondence, H (Box 49, Folder 1.8)
  - Correspondence, I-J (Box 49, Folder 1.9)
  - Correspondence. K (Box 49, Folder 1.10)
    On Reel 58 of the Wald Microfilm
  - Correspondence, L (Box 49, Folder 1.11)
  - Correspondence, M (Box 50, Folder 1.1)
  - Correspondence, Me (Box 50, Folder 1.2)
  - Correspondence. N (Box 50, Folder 1.3)
  - Correspondence, O (Box 50, Folder 1.4)
  - Correspondence, P (Box 50, Folder 1.5)
  - Correspondence. Q (Box 50, Folder 1.6)
    On Reel 59 of the Wald Microfilm
  - Correspondence. Ra-Ri (Box 50, Folder 1.7)
  - Correspondence, Ro-Ru. (Box 50, Folder 1.8)
  - Correspondence, S (unsorted) (Box 50, Folder 1.9)
  - Correspondence, S-SO (Box 50, Folder 1.10)
  - Correspondence, Sp-Sy (Box 50, Folder 1.11)
  - Correspondence. T (Box 50, Folder 1.12)
    On Reel 60 of the Wald Microfilm
  - Correspondence, U (Box 51, Folder 1.1)
  - Correspondence, V (Box 51, Folder 1.2)
  - Correspondence, W-We (Box 51, Folder 1.3)
  - Correspondence, Wh-Wr (Box 51, Folder 1.4)
  - Correspondence, Y-Z (Box 51, Folder 1.5)
  - Country places, general: 1926 and n.d. (Box 51, Folder 2.1)
  - Country places, general: 1928 (Box 51, Folder 2.2)
  - Country places, general: 1929 (Box 51, Folder 2.3)
  - Country places, general: 1930 (Box 51, Folder 2.4)
  - Country places. general: 1931 (Box 51, Folder 2.5)
    On Reel 61 of the Wald Microfilm
  - Country places. general: 1932 (Box 51, Folder 2.6)
  - Country places. general: 1933 (Box 51, Folder 2.7)
  - Country places. Blossom Farm (Box 51, Folder 2.8)
  - Country places, Camp Henry (Box 52, Folder 1.1)
  - Country places, Camp Henry: Robert Rubio (Box 52, Folder 1.2)
  - Country places, Camp Tapawingo (Box 52, Folder 1.3)
    On Reel 62 of the Wald Microfilm
  - Country places, construction (Box 52, Folder 1.4)
  - Country places. Counselors' Training Course (Box 52, Folder 1.5)
  - Country places, Echo Hill Farm: 1922 (Box 52, Folder 1.6)
  - Country places, Echo Hill Farm: 1926 (Box 52, Folder 1.7)
  - Country places, Echo Hill Farm: 1927 (Box 52, Folder 1.8)
  - Country places, Echo Hill Farm: 1928 (Box 52, Folder 1.9)
  - Country places, Echo Hill Farm: 1929 (Box 52, Folder 1.10)
  - Country places, Echo Hill Farm: 1930 (Box 52, Folder 1.11)
  - Country places, Echo Hill Farm: 1931 (Box 52, Folder 1.12)
  - Country places, Echo Hill Farm: 1932 (Box 52, Folder 1.13)
    On Reel 63 of the Wald Microfilm
  - Country places, Echo Hill Farm: 1933 (Box 52, Folder 1.14)
  - Country places, Echo Hill Farm: 1936 and n.d. (Box 52, Folder 1.15)
  - Country places, financial: 1 (Box 53, Folder 1.1)
  - Country places, financial: 2 (Box 53, Folder 1.2)
  - Country places, financial: R.B. Tilatnikoff (Box 53, Folder 1.3)
  - Country places, photographs (Box 53, Folder 1.4)
  - Country places, Riverholm and The Rest (Box 53, Folder 1.5)
  - Dental Clinic (Box 53, Folder 2)
  - Economic Group (Box 53, Folder 3)
  - Financial, general: 1923-1925 (Box 53, Folder 4.1)
  - Financial, general: 1926 (Box 53, Folder 4.2)
    On Reel 64 of the Wald Microfilm
  - Financial, general: J927 (Box 53, Folder 4.3)
  - Financial, general: 1928 (Box 53, Folder 4.4)
  - Financial, general: 1929 (Box 53, Folder 4.5)
  - Financial. general: 1930 (Box 53, Folder 4.6)
  - Financial, general: 1931 (Box 53, Folder 4.7)
  - Financial, general: 1932-1933 (Box 53, Folder 4.8)
  - Financial, general: stafJ926 (Box 53, Folder 4.9)
  - Financial, general: staff, J927 (Box 53, Folder 4.10)
  - Financial, general: staff, J928 (Box 53, Folder 4.11)
  - Financial. general: staff, 1929-1932 (Box 53, Folder 4.12)
  - Financial records, accounts: 1912-1926 loose pages (Box 54)
  - Financial records, accounts: 1912-1926. bound ledger 1 (Box 54)
    On Reel 65 of the Wald Microfilm
  - Financial records. accounts: 1912-1926. loose pages (Box 54)
  - Financial records. accounts: 1912-1926 bound ledger 2 (Box 54)
  - Financial records. accounts: 1928-1931 (Box 55, Folder 1.1)
  - Financial records, accounts: J933 (Box 55, Folder 1.2)
  - Financial records, accounts: 1933-1934 (Box 55, Folder 1.3)
  - Financial records, American Union Bank (Box 55, Folder 1.4)
  - Financial records. Associated Gas &: Electric System (Box 55, Folder 1.5)
  - Financial records, automobile (Box 55, Folder 1.6)
  - Financial records. bills (Box 55, Folder 1.7)
  - Financial records. Bronx House account (Box 55, Folder 1.8)
    On Reel 66 of the Wald Microfilm
  - Financial records, budget 1920 (Box 55, Folder 1.9)
  - Financial records, budget 1921-1922 (Box 55, Folder 1.10)
  - Financial records, budget 1923 (Box 55, Folder 1.11)
  - Financial records. budget 1924 (Box 55, Folder 1.12)
  - Financial records, budget 1925 (Box 55, Folder 1.13)
  - Financial records, budget 1926-1927 (Box 55, Folder 1.14)
  - Financial records, budget 1928-1929 (Box 55, Folder 1.15)
  - Financial records, budget 1930-1932 (Box 55, Folder 1.16)
  - Financial records. check stubs: 1926-1928 (Box 55, Folder 1.17)
  - Financial. donations: 1905-1909 and n.d. (Box 56, Folder 1.1)
  - Financial. donations: 1910-1911 (Box 56, Folder 1.2)
  - Financial. donations: 1912-1914 (Box 56, Folder 1.3)
  - Financial. donations: 1915-1917 (Box 56, Folder 1.4)
  - Financial, donations: 19J8-1919 (Box 56, Folder 1.5)
  - Financial, donations: 1920 (Box 56, Folder 1.6)
  - Financial, donations: 1922-1923 (Box 56, Folder 1.7)
  - Financial, donations: 1924-1926 (Box 56, Folder 1.8)
    On Reel 67 of the Wald Microfilm
  - Financial. donations: 1927 (Box 56, Folder 1.9)
  - Financial, donations: 1928 (Box 56, Folder 1.10)
  - Financial, donations: 1929-1930 (Box 56, Folder 1.11)
  - Financial, donations: 1931 (Box 56, Folder 1.12)
  - Financial, donations: 1932-1933 (Box 56, Folder 1.13)
  - Financial. donations: Altman Foundation (Box 56, Folder 1.14)
  - Financial, donations: Anderson (Box 56, Folder 1.15)
  - Financial, donations: Bourne (Box 56, Folder 1.16)
  - Financial, donations: Burke Foundation (Box 56, Folder 1.17)
  - Financial, donations: Goldenberg (Box 56, Folder 1.18)
  - Financial, donations: Harkness (Box 56, Folder 1.19)
  - Financial, donations: Havens Relief Fund (Box 56, Folder 1.20)
  - Financial, donations: Junior League (Box 56, Folder 1.21)
  - Financial, donations: Neustadt (Box 56, Folder 1.22)
  - Financial, donations: Pratt (Box 56, Folder 1.23)
  - Financial, donations: Rockefeller (Box 56, Folder 1.24)
  - Financial, donations: Seligman (Box 56, Folder 1.25)
  - Financial, donations: Simonton (Box 56, Folder 1.26)